No judgement taken, my guy. I heard my
body was a temple, so I just figured I'd
put a good sign on it. This is not a
tattoo, it tells a story and it's a
story from my favorite book as a child,
St. George and the Dragon. Children's
books have changed a lot since I was a
kid, but in this one George fights the
dragon for 3 days. The dragon pierces
him and burns him and casts him down and
every night a lovely woman named Uma
comes and nurses him and he regains his
strength overnight and he continues
fighting the dragon until he kills it.
And then after he kills the dragon, he's
offered Uma's hand in marriage, right
here. And you know what George said?
Nah, I have sworn 7 years of service to
the fairy godmother. I'm going to go
take care of that and I'll be back. And
you know, that has stuck with me since I
was a kid. It's a gangster book. You
have to have your children read good
books at a young age. One day it'll be
written on the tablet of their heart.
And to me, this is me fighting the
system. That's little old tiny me. And
this is the system with his teeth and
his claws and his fire and everything
and I'm just doing all I can, hold my
own. And I figured I'd put it on my
chest, kind of like Conor McGregor. Cuz
when Conor McGregor got to the UFC, his
first fight with Marcus McGrim, if you
look at him, he was timid and pale, he
was a scared little kid. He didn't have
no tattoos, but after he'd been there a
little while and he realized that that
left hand could put the best in the
world to sleep,
he tattooed a dragon on his chest and
became a new man.
So, I'm just following suit. Sending
love from Costa Rica. I run off of two
things, sun power
and sun power. Catch my drift?